"Sea God's Palace Land"
So last weekend, we went
swimming together, which was fine, but...
でさ この前の週末に一緒に泳ぎに行ったのはいいんだけどさ
Sorry I'm late!
お待たせ
No problem!
Let's go together, okay?
一度行こうよ ね
All right, let's say next Sunday.
じゃあ 来週の日曜日にするか
The season of happy kids...
リア充の季節か
I'm home...
ただいま
- Hot out there...
- Raysis! Wait!
ああ 暑かった
What's wrong, Guernica? Fight back!
Raysis, why?
- Why, you ask? That's a silly question.
- Kobato, you're not using the air conditioner?
小鳩 お前 エアコンは
Raysis!
Bro...
あんちゃん
WANAWANA
Gutto Good hajiketeru
グッと Good 弾ける
Angai nandai hamatten jan
案外なんだい ハマってんじゃん
Hito mishiri shiteru hima ni hajimeyou!
人見知りしてる暇に 始めよう
Tomodachi tsukucchatte asonjatte Yeh!
友達 作っちゃって遊んじゃって Yeah
"Haganai"
クールに見えて 実は超寂しい
Kuuru ni miete, jitsu wa chou sabishii
(Mosou nara bai, bai, bai
Shinyuu nara inai, inai, inai, inai)
妄想ならバイバイバイ
親友なら いないいないいないいない
Nani fujiyuu naku, dakedo tarinai
何不自由なく だけど足りない
(Riajuu kara tooi, tooi, tooi?
Shinyuu nara inai, inai, inai, inai)
リア充から遠い遠い遠い
親友なら いないいないいないいない
Zannen doushi de atsumattara
残念同士で 集まったら
Ah- yosou ga dekinai
Ah- 予想が出来ない 展開の 地雷を踏んだ
Tenkai no jirai wo funda!
SOWASOWA
Zettai, zettai nozokitai
絶対絶対覗きたい
Koukai hyakkai shitakunaitte
後悔100回したくないって
Tsumannai puraido nante
sutekicchatte furikicchatte
つまんない プライドなんて
てきっちゃって 振りきっちゃって
Zannen kannen shite mitara,
angai nandai hamatten jan
残念観念してみたら
案外なんだいハマってんじゃん
Butsukatte, dogimagi atte, mitsukeyou!
ぶつかって どぎまぎ合って 見つけよう
Tomodachi tsukucchatte asonjatte Yeh!
友達 作っちゃって遊んじゃって Yeah
Zettai, zettai nozokitai
絶対絶対覗きたい
YOU！ 捨てきっちゃって 振りきっちゃって
You! Sutekicchatte furikicchatte
Yes！ どーだいどーだいそこんとこ
Yes! Doudai? Doudai, sokontoko
本字幕由诸神卖萌组(kamigami.org)出品 仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途
---诸神卖萌组---
日听:安少    翻译:银苹果    校对:喵儿&小草爱吃梨   时间轴&后期:亢奋的蛇
Here it comes!
"School Swimsuits Don't Appear"
Okay, I'm back.
おーい 戻ったぞ
Did you buy a new A/C?!
クーラー買ってきてくれたと
ああ でも取り付けは３日後だとさ
Yeah, but they won't come to
install it for another three days.
Th-Three days?!
み…３日
ククク まったく人間どもは使えぬな
Honestly, humans are worthless...
How interesting...
おもしろい
Then, for the time being, shall we
make merry at this purgatorial feast?
では今しばらくの間 この煉獄の供宴に興じるとしようか
ククク 我が名はレイシス・ヴィ・フェリシティ・煌
My name is Raysis Vi Felicity Sumeragi!
Even if I were to be surrounded
by 20-million-degree flames,
たとえこの身を２千万度の炎で焼かれようと
I would still be the great King of
the Night, as hale and hearty as ever...
ぴんぴんしちょる偉大なる夜の王じゃけん
もっと薄着にしたらどうだ
Why don't you put on something lighter?
This dress embodies my powers of darkness.
このドレスは我が闇の力が具現化したもの
I can't just change into something else.
簡単に替えることなどできぬ
All right, whatever. Want some barley tea?
はいはい 麦茶飲むか
Have I seen this before?
こんな回あったか
Oh. Yesterday's recording...
あっ 昨日の録画か
Here.
ほら
I never thought I would be
backed into a corner like this...
この我をここまで追い込むとはな
Gaze upon my true form!
見よ 我が真の姿を
Releasing binding spell!
拘束術式解除
Unleashing magic power!
魔力 解放
This is my true form!
これが我の真の姿だ
Your... true form?!
これが真の姿
So the conclusion is next week, huh?
決着は来週か
Let's Go!
Bro!
あんちゃん
R-Releasing b-binding spell!
こ… 拘束じゅちゅ… じゅちゅ
じゅ…つ式 解除
Watch me!
ちゃんと見といてよ
Put everything you took off in the washer.
脱いだ物は洗濯機に入れろよ
Right!
All right!
U-Unleashing magic power!
ま…魔力解放
ククク これが我の真の姿だ
This is my true form!
A ripoff?
パクリ
It's not a ripoff!
パクリやないもん
ククク 我が真の力を解放することになろうとはな
I didn't want it to be necessary
to unleash my true power...
Chalk it up to an annoying season of hell,
さすがいまいましき地獄の季節 といったところか
I suppose...
Well, that's fine with me, but...
まあ別にいいけど
Oh, Kobato, I'm heading out to
the club. Do you wanna go with?
小鳩 これから部活行くけど
一緒に来るか
You can go out wearing that, right?
それなら外出られるだろう
And the club's got a working air conditioner...
部室はクーラーも効いてるし
I'll go!
行く
Kobato...
小鳩
Those are your clothes from
elementary school, aren't they?
それ お前が小学生のときの服だよな
That you can wear them with no problem
even as a 2nd-year middle school student
中二になっても問題なく着れるって
maybe means you're not growing?
お前 もしかして成長が
W-W-What should I do, Bro?!
どッ ど…どげんしよう あんちゃん
ウチもう大きくなれへん
I'm not getting any bigger?!
N-Now that I think about it, as a
member of the Night Tribe, I am eternal.
か…考えてみれば
我は悠久の時を生きる夜の貴族
My body will never get
discrepant or ugly with age.
我が肉体は永遠においさばらえることなどないのだ
I see...
そうか
I'm glad you won't get discrepant.
さばらえないでよかったな
Yep.
It's "get decrepit," Kobato.
老いさらばえるだぞ 小鳩
Hi.
うーッす
You're late!
遅いぞ
Welcome back, Aniki.
お疲れさまです あにき
お兄ちゃん
Big Brother!
Hey, long time no see!
おお 久しぶり
あのな あのな
Listen to this! Today,
Yukimura got me sushi for lunch!
今日は幸村がお寿司を食べさせてくれたのだ
And yesterday I had steak!
Yukimura is a good guy!
昨日はステーキだったし 幸村はいいヤツだ
Wha? Sushi? Stea...
寿司 ステーッ
Since you ordered me to
give Maria food that tastes good,
マリア殿がおいしく召し上がれるものというご命令でしたゆえ
I've been preparing lunches
for her with all my heart and soul.
全身全霊をもって ご用意いたしました
S-Sure, I said that, but you're going overboard!
確かに そうは言ったが
そりゃ やりすぎだろう
When you force-fed me that weird medicine,
変な薬を食べさせられたときは
「このオカマ野郎 ちょん切ってやる」と神に誓ったけど
I swore to God that I would
"chop something off of that homo"!
But now, it's different!
今は違うのだ
Thank you, Yukimura!
ありがとな 幸村
Please thank Aniki.
お礼はあにきへどうぞ
Thank you! I love you, Big Brother!
ありがとう
お兄ちゃん だ～い好き
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
あほ～ あほう あほう
I hope my bro hates you,
getting fattened up like a pig!
あんたなんか ブタみたいにブクブク肥えて
あんちゃんに嫌われればええんじゃ
W-What was that?!
な…何だと
あっ お前誰だ
Who the hell are you?
I'm Bro's little sister!
ウチはあんちゃんの妹じゃ
あッ あ～ん 小鳩ちゃん
Kobato-chan!
お前 吸血鬼か 騙したな
You're that vampire?! You fooled me!
Despised incarnation of darkness!
いまわしき闇の化身め
- Begone! Begone! Begone!
- Ow! Ow!
消えろ
イタイタ おのれ
Why, you!
あっ 吸血鬼が噛んだ
A vampire bit me!
Why would you bite me?! Dummy! Dummy!
何で噛むのだ あほ あほあほ うんこうんこ
Of course she bit you.
そりゃ 噛むだろう 吸血鬼は
That's what vampires do.
That's what you get, tool of God!
知っているか 神の手先よ
Those who are bitten by
vampires become kin to the vampires!
吸血鬼に噛まれた者は 吸血鬼の眷属となってしまうのだ
I-Is that true, Big Brother?!
ほ…本当なのか お兄ちゃん
I have heard that before.
確かにそういう話はあるな
I'm gonna turn into a vampire!
私は吸血鬼になってしまったのだ
Maria? I've heard if you bathe in the
sun's rays right after getting bitten,
マリア 噛まれてすぐに太陽の光をたくさん浴びれば
you won't become a vampire.
吸血鬼にならずにすむらしいぞ
Really?!
本当なのか
It's true.
本当だ
Although it won't work if you wear
clothes. You have to be totally naked.
ただし服を着ていたら意味がないから 全裸でな
Got it! Thank you, Yozora!
分かった ありがとう夜空
You're evil...
お前な
She really is a moron.
あいつは本当に頭が悪いな
What?
何だ 我の姿をジロジロ見るな
Stop staring at me!
Kobato-chan, you're adorable!
小鳩ちゃん かわいい～
Tell me, why did you give up the
Goth-Lolita look? To change your image?
ねえ 何でゴスロリやめたの イメチェン
I unleashed my true power.
真の力を解放したのだ
アハ～ 意味分かんないけど やっぱりかわいい～
I don't know what you mean,
but you're so darn cute!
You're cute every time I see you!
相変わらず イタかわいいわ～
Bro...
あんちゃん
Little missy, what kind
of panties are you wearing?
お嬢ちゃん 今どんなパンツ履いてるの
Both of you, come on...
お前らな
Let's take them off, okay?!
さあ 脱ぎ脱ぎしましょうね
I wonder how I'll be able
to conquer Kobato-chan...
どうやったら小鳩ちゃん攻略できるのかしら
Behave yourselves, perverts!
いいかげんにしろ 変態ども
あははは… 光だ～
Light!!
God's light!
神の光なのだ あはは ははは…
Still, there's nothing to
do during summer vacation.
しっかし夏休みってのは暇だな
Yeah. So little, I wouldn't mind
うむ 夏休み中の宿題が
if we'd been given ten times
the amount of summer homework.
あと１０倍あってもいいくらいだ
That, I can do without.
それは勘弁してくれ
We've got all this time on our hands.
こんなに暇なのに
I wonder how other people are killing time...
他の連中は どうやって時間を潰しているのだろう
They're having fun with
their friends, of course...
そりゃ友達と遊びに…
I wish all the happy people would just die...
リア充はみんな死ねばいいのに
"Wow, look! Look! The pool is huge!!"
I wish they'd die, too...
あいつらも死なないかな
Don't have murderous
thoughts about game characters.
ゲームキャラに殺意を向けるなよ
ふん 私があのゲームの作者だったら
If I were the writer of that game,
I'd put a shark in the scene.
あのシーンでサメを出す
A shark?
サメ
What are you being so nasty for?
なに物騒なこと言ってんのよ
"I'm gonna swim with you, Mizuki!"
If a shark suddenly appeared in that scene
そのシーンでいきなりサメが出てきて
and made a big bloody mess
as it devoured those girls,
女どもを食い散らかしてくれたら
I would recognize that as a godly game.
神ゲー認定してやってもいいのだが
A stupid development
like that would never happen!
そんなバカな展開になるわけないでしょう
In the first place, this scene is at a pool!
そもそも このシーンはプールよ
"...is waiting for you by the pool."
キャー サメよ
"Shark!"
ふふん どうせ本物のサメなんかじゃないんでしょ
I'm sure it's not a real shark.
It's either Marina's radio-controlled
one or a stuffed animal...
マリナのラジコンとか 着ぐるみとかってオチね
Anyway, it's one of those cliché events.
まあ ベタなお約束イベントってやつ
"What's a real great white shark doing here?!"
なんで本物のホオジロサメが
Why?!
何でなのよ
I-It's okay! This is a comedy!
だ…大丈夫 これはコメディーなんだから
In a comedy, it's possible to have
a shark suddenly show up at a pool.
コメディーなら いきなりプールにサメが出てくるギャグもあり
I predict the main character
will kick the shark's ass...
あたしの予想では きっとこのサメを主人公がやっつけて
And everyone's favorable ratings will go up!
みんなの好感度アップ
イヤ～ッ
"Mizuki!!!"
No!! Mizuki!!
イヤ～ッ ミズキ～
Well, that was a godly game.
まあ 神ゲーだったな
I've had enough of this shitty game!
クソゲーにもほどがあるわよ
That was St. Jaws Academy Tale, right?
今の「聖ジョーズ学園物語」ですね
Yeah, so?
そうだけど
The rumors were right, then, that it has a
really extreme bad ending.
噂どおりのすごいバッドエンドですね
If you fail to set up the flags in St. Jaws,
ジョー学 フラグの立て方に失敗すると
it not only plunges you into a bad ending,
容赦なくバッドエンドに突入する上に
but finishes with a brutal scene
that comes totally out of left field!
そのバッドエンドが ことごとく何の脈絡もない残虐シーンで終わるので
In a sense, the game is
supposedly famous for being stupid.
ある意味 バカゲーとして有名らしいです
Even the world of girl games is deep.
ギャルゲーの世界も奥が深いな
"St. Jaws Academy Tale"
Even so, I wanna go to a pool.
それにしても プールに行きたいわね
Huh?
はあ プールでヒロイン達がサメに食い殺されるシーンを見た直後にその発言
You say that right after seeing a
scene of heroines devoured at the pool?
Do you have a death wish?
貴様は自殺願望でもあるのか
How does that follow?!
何でそうなるのよ
It doesn't have anything to
do with that dumbass game,
別にさっきのクソゲーは関係なく
I just wanna go to a pool.
プールに行きたいなって思っただけよ
Oh...
なんだ てっきり貴様が
I was worried
本気で食用肉としての自覚に目覚めてしまったのかと思って心配したぞ
that your eyes were opened to the
joys of being a predatory carnivore.
Be grateful to me!
感謝しろ
Th-Thank you...
あ…ありがとう
I wanna go to the pool, too...
プール ウチも行きたい
Kobato-chan, you wanna go to the pool?!
小鳩ちゃん プールに行きたいの
Then let's go together!
じゃあ あたしとプールに行きましょう
That's just creepy, Meat!
キモいぞ 肉
A pool, huh? The hangout of the happy people...
プールか
リア充どもの巣窟だな
If I made friends, the pool
would be a place I could go to...
友達ができたら プールに行くこともあるか
It isn't something that
requires a lot of thought.
難しく考えることないじゃない
I went to Sea God's
Palace Land before with Koda...
竜宮ランドなら あたし 小鷹と
Nothing!
まあ 隣人部の活動として
W-Well, why don't we all go
there together, as a club activity?
みんなで行ってみるのもいいんじゃないか
Like a rehearsal for the real thing...
予行演習みたいな感じで
That's not a bad idea...
それもそうだな
It's not like we've got anything
better to do. Maybe we should go...
どうせ暇だし 行ってみるか
Yay!
やった
- Kodaka-sempai, don't get too excited
when you see Rika in her swimsuit, okay?
- You'll go with me to the pool, right, Kobato-chan?
小鷹先輩 理科の水着姿に興奮しないでくださいね
- I bet you wear one of those things,
like a white dress over your swimsuit, right?
- You'll go with me to the pool, right, Kobato-chan?
どうせ お前アレだろう 水着の上に白衣とかのイロモノ担当だろ
- I bet you wear one of those things,
like a white dress over your swimsuit, right?
- Still creepy, Meat!
W-Why would you think that?
なぜ それを
Since you say so, Rika will
choose a really sexy swimsuit
こうなったら うんとセクシーな水着を選んで
to make you irresistibly
drawn to her charms, Sempai!
先輩を悩殺してあげますからね
Low leg cut,
ローレグ ヒモビキニ ブラジル水着 バンソウコウ 全裸
string bikini,
brassiere swimsuit,
Band-Aids,
nude,
pride!
プライド
最後の三つは何なんだ
- What the hell were the last three?
- I don't understand you, Meat!
"I did an indecent act. I'm sorry."
Looks like she's having fun...
楽しそうだな
先輩
Sempai!
Over here!
こっちで～す
You're all here early.
みんな早いなあ
あんたが遅いのよ
You're late!
待ち合わせはここじゃないだろ
We're not supposed to meet here.
It was like this when we got here.
私達が着いたときには 既にこのありさまでな
What's with this rush hour traffic?!
何だ このラッシュ状態は
Yozora, are you okay? You look sick.
夜空 顔色悪いぞ 大丈夫か
I am...
酔った
It's not from the bus. It's the crowd of people.
バスじゃない 人混みにだ
I feel sick...
気持ち悪い
Here.
ほら
Don't need it. I'm not gonna throw up...
無用だ 吐かない
I'm definitely not gonna throw up...
私は絶対に吐かない
R-Rika will do her best, too...
理科も頑張ります
お前もか
You too?
A sh-shut-in in this crowd...
引きこもりに この混雑は
But I'll be fine...
でも平気です
If I have to, I'll get energy
いざとなれば 小鷹先輩の下半身で
エネルギーを補充します
from Kodaka-sempai below the belt!
そッ そうか
I-I see...
By the way, when Yozora-sempai
says, "I'm not gonna throw up,"
ところで夜空先輩が「吐かない 吐かない」って言うと
何だか興奮しますね
it's kind of a turn-on, isn't it?
調子悪いのかいいのか どっちなんだお前は
Are you sick or feeling good? Make up your mind!
Kobato-chan, what do you
wanna do when we get to the pool?
小鳩ちゃん
プールに着いたら何がしたい
Swim...
泳ぐ
そりゃそうよね
Of course, right?
Shall I teach you how to swim?
ね あたしが泳ぎを教えてあげようか
No, I can swim already.
いい 泳げる
You can swim! What are you good at?
泳げるんだ 何が得意
Long-distance...
遠泳
Then why don't we swim long-distance together?!
じゃあ 一緒に遠泳しよっか
イヤ
No!
I love how unfriendly she is, too!
つれないところが またいいわ
She's a " tough on the outside,
tender on the inside" type!
これがツンデレってやつなのね
A-Are you okay?!
大丈夫
助けて あんちゃん
Help me, Bro!
どこかぶつけなかった
Did you bump into something?
- Look how cute they are...
- Kobato-chan?
スゲーかわいいよな
ね 小鳩ちゃん
They look alike. Maybe they're sisters?
似てるよな 姉妹かな
"Sea God's Palace Land"
We finally made it...
やっと着いたか
Sempai...
先輩
See, Kodaka? Told you
I wasn't gonna throw up...
どうだ小鷹 吐かなかっただろう
ああ えらいえらい
Yeah. Very admirable.
Yozora-sempai didn't throw up...
吐いてない夜空先輩 はあはあ…
Anyway, look at all these people...
にしても すごい人ね
It wasn't like this the last time I was here.
前に来たときはこんなじゃなかったのに
I guess it's just so hot that
even commoners flock to the pool.
やっぱり暑いから庶民どももプールに群がってきたのかしら
Cursed sun!
クッ いまいましい太陽め
But now that I'm in my
true form, it can't destroy me!
しかし 真の姿になった我を滅ぼすことなどできぬわ
I wanna get in the pool quick!
早うプール入りたい
Aniki...
あにき
"Sea God's Palace Land"
"Admittance 50% Off!!" "Only in August"
So this is the reason it's so crowded...
これが混雑の理由か
We're totally risking our lives being here.
完全に捨て身ね
We should've come in July.
７月に来ればよかった
Well, it's cheap, right?
まあ 安いからいいじゃないか
I'd rather pay double to get
in than have to be in a crowd!
人混みに行くくらいなら 倍の料金を払った方がマシだ
And to hell with sales
or special early-bird offers!
バーゲンとかタイムサービスも滅びればいい
それはそれで困るな
That wouldn't do me any good...
Anyway, shall we go?
とりあえず行くか
"Child" "Adult" "Adult"
"Dispensing Slot"
Sorry to keep you waiting. Here.
待たせたな はい
Then let's meet in front of
the showers after changing.
じゃあ 着替えたらシャワーの前で
Sure.
女
A woman?!
Aniki, I guess I am a wimp
who's hated by all boys...
あにき やはりわたくしは男の人に嫌われる軟弱者なのでしょうか
No, that's not what it is...
いや そういうんじゃなくて
あっ こう見えてもこいつは
D-Despite the way he looks,
this guy is a full-fledged... guy!
れっきとした男…ゴホ ゴホ
Uh... Um...
あッ あの…
That's my Aniki.
さすがあにきです
I suppose this is fine.
ここでいいか
So should we get changed?
それじゃあ着替えるか
はい あにき
Yes, Aniki.
Why is your swimsuit a woman's?!
何で水着まで女物なんだよ
Yozora told me to wear a girl's swimsuit, too.
夜空のあねごが 水着も女性用にせよと
Why would you consult Yozora about a swimsuit?
何で夜空に水着の相談をする
Yozora-anego is my adviser.
[anego: elder sister/boss's wife]
あねごはわたくしのアドバイザーですゆえ
But I also want my inner masculinity
女中さんの格好よりも
to shine through even when
wearing women's clothing,
更に内面の男らしさが求められるとのことなので
so I thought I'd challenge
myself whenever I can.
何事もチャレンジしてみようかと
That's too much of a challenge!
チャレンジしすぎだ
I did bring along a men's
swimsuit too, just in case...
一応 男物の水着も持ってきたのですが
Heave-ho!
That's...
それは
はい ふんどしというものです
Yes. A loincloth.
Please go with the woman's
swimsuit, please, please.
女物の水着にしてくださいお願いします
Then I'll let you wear the loincloth, Aniki.
では こちらのふんどしはあにきに
遠慮しておく
I'll pass!
Say, Kobato-chan, shall I help you change?
ねえねえ 小鳩ちゃん
着替え 手伝ってあげよっか
No!
イヤ
All... right...
Need a hand?
手伝おうか
Yes, please.
はい お願いします
落ち着け俺 こいつは男なんだ
C-Calm down, Kodaka... He's a man!
You're set.
いいぞ
Thank you, Aniki.
助かりました あにき
Sure...
Certainly, it's hard putting on clothes
like that and taking them off alone...
確かに ひとりでは着るのも脱ぐのも大変だな
どうかしたのですか あにき
Is something wrong, Aniki?
Why are you hiding your chest?!
何で胸を隠す
I'm embarrassed about not having a defined chest.
胸板が厚くないので恥ずかしいのです
But if you want to see, Aniki...
しかし あにきがご覧になりたいとおっしゃるならば
I'm not gonna look! Just forget
about it and get the swimsuit on!
ご覧にならない
気にせず着替えを続けてくれ
分かりました
Understood.
Why are the men so late?
何で男子の方が遅いのよ
すまん
Sorry. It took a little time to change.
着替えにちょっと手間取ってな
Why is even his swimsuit a woman's?!
何で水着まで女物なの
Don't ask me...
俺に言われても困る
Huh?
あれ 夜空と理科は
Where are Yozora and Rika?
They said they'll come
after resting a little while.
ちょっと休んでから来るって
Yeah, it looked like
they were both done in.
ああ 相当まいってたみたいだからな
I'm gonna swim first!
先に泳ぐ
It's cold!
ああ 冷た～い
Hurry up, Bro!
あんちゃん 早う
Coming.
うーん これは…
This is...
...more crowded than we imagined, huh?
予想以上の混雑ね
I can't swim long-distance...
遠泳できへん
それは難しそうですね
Yes, I think that would be difficult.
ふん うっとうしいわね 大衆どもが
The common herd is so annoying...
I wish a shark would appear...
サメでも出ないかしら
リアルまでクソゲーにする気かよ
You'd have a crap game intrude on reality?
When Yozora and Rika get here,
夜空達が来たら 流れるプールとかウォータースライダーの方に行ってみるか
how about heading over to
the lazy river and water slide?
ふん 前と大違い
It's totally different from last time.
そうだな
Yep...
Just the two of us came then, right?
あのときは俺達二人で来たっけ
Uh... Yeah...
うん そうだったわね
That's right...
And you got mad at me...
それでお前 俺に怒ってたよな
After all, you...
だってあれは小鷹があたしに…
That doesn't bother me.
それはいいんだ
It's just, as we parted ways...
ただ 帰りにお前さ
...why did you say, "Thank you"?
何で「ありがとう」って
あ～あ もう夜空達遅いわね
Jeez, Yozora and Rika are taking a while, huh?
そうだな
Yeah...
I'll go check on them.
あたし ちょっと見てくる
What's she flustered about?
何か慌ててんな
I see... At the time, there were
only three of us in the Neighbors Club...
そっか あのときって隣人部は３人だったんだよな
We've got more members now...
今は部員も増えたもんな
I can't say we've fulfilled
our goal of making friends yet,
まだ目的である友達ができたとは言えないが
but depending on how you look at it,
maybe we have changed a lot.
考えようによっては結構変わったのかな
Kodaka!
小鷹
I got this text from Yozora!
夜空から こんなメールが
"I'm going home. Rika, too."
Yozora!
夜空
Kodaka!
小鷹
Bro?
あんちゃん
Yozora! Rika!
夜空 理科
Hey! Wait, Yozora!
ちょっと 待ちなさいよ 夜空
That idiot...
あのバカ
And I was gonna show off my
elegant swimming form to her...
せっかくあたしの華麗な泳ぎを見せつけてやろうと思ってたのに
"We're waiting for your next visit."
Maybe we haven't changed...
まだ変わってないのかな
Kodaka?
小鷹
あっ いや
Nothing...
Should we go home?
帰ろっか
Yeah...
The Neighbors Club activity report...
隣人部活動記録
"We're waiting for your next visit."
Today's activity:
本日の活動
Nothing...
なし
あー 脳內 想像理想の 現実逃避
Aa, nounai souzou risou no genjitsu touhi
今更どっちだっていっけど 友達作り
Ima sara docchi datte ikkedo... tomodachi zukuri
一人寂しい奴だと蔑む 視線が気になる
Hitori sabishii yatsu da to
sagesumu shisen ga ki ni naru
で 上っ面だけ集まったら
De, uwattsura dake atsumattara...
それでいいと 思っているうちに
Sore de ii to omotte iru uchi ni~
あれよあれよと登場 揃って 破天荒な奴らに
Are yo are yo to toujou, sorotte
Hatenkou na yatsura ni
Maipeesu midasarete yuku
マイペース 乱されてゆく 頭くる！特に憎っくき肉
Atama kuru! Toku ni nikukkuki niku!
Watashi no mune, hisoka
ni asette yuujou fudan kimi de
私の胸秘かに焦って 優柔不斷気味で
My heart 伝えられない 殘念なのは 私なのか
My heart tsutaerarenai
Zannen na no wa watashi na no ka?
もやもやを かきわけ Today！
Moya moya wo kakiwake Today!
Okizari ni sareta otome
gokoro ano hi kara kuyande iru
置き去りにされた 乙女心 あの日から悔やんでいる
早く見つけ出して 迷子のココロ
Hayaku mitsuke dashite, maigo no kokoro
Here's shabu-shabu.
シャブシャブでございます
Meat! Meat!
お肉お肉
Here's some sushi.
お寿司でございます
Roe! Salmon roe! Fatty tuna!
ウニ いくら 大トロ
Here's steak.
ステーキでございます
Marbled! Delicious!
霜降りうま～い
Here's broiled eel over rice.
うな重でございます
ご飯が見えない
I can't even see the rice! Wow! Yummy!
すごい うまいのだ しゅごい
Wonderful!
I can't move anymore!
動けなくなっちゃったのだ
A-A dream! I just had a scary dream!
夢 うわ～ん 怖い夢を見たのだ
Next time: "The President's
Recollections are Painful."
"Next time: The President's Recollections are Painful"
次回「理事長は追想が切ない」
ごちそう怖いのだ
I'm scared to eat!